A Guide to the Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 1 FA078
Rockefeller Archive Center
- American Universities Research Program, 1956-1970; 2
  - American Universities Research Program - Workshops, 2.2
    - Research on Economics of Agricultural Development in East and West Africa, June 9-14, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - American Universities Research Program - Grants, 2.3
    - Agricultural and Technical College of North Carolina - Williams, Frederick A. (65-) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - University of Arizona - Baker, Simon (63-11) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - University of Arizona - Hillman, Jimmye S. (63-50) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bradley University - Stoner, George E. Jr. (65-52) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Brandeis University - Roos, Leslie L. Jr. (68-2) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Brandeis University - Weckstein, Richard S. (66-32) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - University of British Columbia - Bell, Peter (68-14) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - University of British Columbia - Quirin, David (63-37) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - University of California (Berkeley) - Jorgenson, Dale W. (66-49) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - University of California (Berkeley) - McEntire, Davis (64-11) (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - University of California (Berkeley) - McEntire, Davis (65-19) (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - University of California (Davis) - Chancellor, William (67-43) (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - University of California (Davis) - Chancellor, William (67-43) (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - University of California (Davis) - Cohen, Yehudi A. (65-40) (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - University of California (Davis) - Kaneda, Hiromitsu (67-39) (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - University of California (Davis) - McCorkle, C.O. Jr. (66-30) (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - University of California (Davis) - Smith, William C. (65-30) (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - University of California (Santa Barbara) - Brokensha, David and Charles Erasmus (68-5) (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - University of California (Santa Barbara) - Wallace, Ben K. (68-1) (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - California State College at Hayward - Clarke, William C. (65-23) (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Carleton College - Langworthy, Russell (67-1) (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - University of Cincinnati - Roder, Wolf (68-6) (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Colgate University - Ludwig, Armin K. (67-24) (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - University of Colorado - MacPhail, Donald D. (66-46) (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - University of Colorado - Owen, Wyn F. (65-26) (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Cornell University - Allee, David J. (64-14) (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Cornell University - Landsberger, H.A. (67-8) (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Cornell University - Landsberger, H.A. (67-8) (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Cornell University - Larson, Olaf F. (63-14) (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Cornell University - Sola, Donald F. (66-9) (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Cornell University - Taylor, Lee (67-18) (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Cornell University - Whyte, William F. (63-42) (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Cornell University - Whyte, William F. (66-48) (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Duquensne University - Deans, Robert H. (65-3) (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - University of Florida - Crist, Raymond (63-24) (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - University of Florida - Davis, George K. (63-5) (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - University of Florida - Grigsby, S.E. (67-30) (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - University of Florida - McPherson, Woodrow W. (63-7) (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - University of Florida - McPherson, Woodrow W. (63-7) (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - University of Florida - Winsberg, Morton D. (66-14) (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - University of Georgia - Bailey, Wilfred C. (66-11) (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - University of Georgia - Belcher, John C. (66-31) (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - University of Georgia - Belcher, John C. (67-29) (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - University of Georgia - Brown, E. Evan (67-54) (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Grinnell College - Voertman, Robert F. (67-16) (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Grinnell College - Voertman, Robert F. (67-16) (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Grinnell College - Voertman, Robert F. (67-16) (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Grinnell College - Voertman, Robert F. (67-16) (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Harvard University - Brothers, D.S. and R. Vernon (66-39) (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - University of Hawaii - Peters, C.W. (65-25) (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - University of Hawaii - Philipp, P.F. (63-16) (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - University of Hawaii - Pitts, Forrest R. (67-20) (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - University of Hawaii - Ross, Edward (65-39) (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - University of Illinois - Brinegar, George K. (63-3) (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - University of Illinois - Fettig, Lyle (65-40) (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - University of Illinois - Schmidt, Stephen C. (66-3) (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Indiana University - Forman, Shepard (67-10) (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - University of Iowa - Andrews, David H. (66-21) (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Iowa State University - Beal, George M. (64-19) (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Iowa State University - Fletcher, Lehman B. (63-17) (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Iowa State University - Kaldor, Donald R. (66-25) (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Iowa State University - Timmons, John F. (67-28) (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Bramhall, David F. (65-14) (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Kansas State University - Douglas, Louis H. (63-43) (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Kansas State University - Kelley, Paul L. (65-10) (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Kansas State University - Sjo, John and George Montgomery (64-9) (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - University of Kentucky - Bondurant, John H. (64-18) (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - University of Kentucky - Redman, John C. (67-14) (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - University of Kentucky - Smith, Eldon D. (67-44) (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Lawrence College - Bessac, Frank B. (64-8) (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Lawrence College - Bessac, Susanne (64-21) (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - University of Maine - Tuthill, Dean F. (63-46) (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - University of Maryland - Foster, Phillips (63-40) (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - University of Maryland - Foster, Phillips (65-9) (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - University of Maryland - Foster, Phillips (67-4) (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - University of Maryland - Moore, John R. (63-28) (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - University of Maryland - Moore, John R. (66-26) (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - University of Maryland - Wysong, John W. (67-27) (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - University of Massachusetts - Crossman, Bradford D. (67-3) (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - University of Massachusetts - Foster, John H. (64-24) (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - University of Massachusetts - Russell, Sargent (65-12) (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - University of Michigan - Clarkson, James D. (67-38) (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - University of Michigan - Ness, Gayl D. (66-40) (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - University of Michigan - Ness, Gayl D.; L.A.P. Gosling and J.D. Clarkson (67-35) (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - University of Michigan - Yengoyan, Aram A. (65-18) (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Michigan State University - Adams, Arthur E. (66-2) (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Michigan State University - Eicher, Carl (63-10) (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Michigan State University - Hunter, John M. (66-10) (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Michigan State University - Luykx, Nicholas G. M. II (67-45) (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Michigan State University - Meaders, O. Donald (67-19) (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - University of Minnesota - Holt, Robert T. (67-46) (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - University of Minnesota - Raup, Philip M. (66-29) (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Mississippi State University - Blair, P.T. and J.A. Baquero (63-21) (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Mississippi State University - Kaufman, Harold F. (64-15) (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - University of Missouri - Campbell, Rex R. (67-2) (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - University of Missouri - Hicks, W. Whitney (64-27) (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - University of Missouri - Lionberger, Herbert F. (66-1) (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - University of Missouri - Lionberger, Herbert F. (66-1) (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Montana State College - Helburn, Nicholas (65-20) (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Montana State College - Lassey, William R. (65-31) (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Montana State College - Lassey, William R. (65-31) (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Montana State College - Lassey, William R. (65-31) (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - North Carolina State - Mayo, Selz C. (65-6) (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - University of North Dakota - Stanley, William R. (65-35) (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Ohio State University - Cartano, David G. (65-46) (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - Ohio State University - Rogers, Everette M. (63-13) (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Oklahoma State University - Edington, Everett D. (64-30) (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Oregon State University - Jensen, J. Granville (67-42) (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - University of Oregon - Johannessen, Carl L. (65-28) (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Fliegel, Frederick C. (66-6) (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Nydegger, William F. (67-37) (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Robbins, Michael C. (67-17) (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Purdue University - Eisgruber, Ludwig (67-21) (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Purdue University - Wiley, Jay W. (63-25) (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - Queen's University - Lele, Jayant K. (66-47) (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - University of South Carolina - Lovingood, Paul E. Jr. (68-13) (Box 11, Folder 116)
    - Southern Illinois University - Haag, Herman A. (63-19) (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - Stanford University - Bateman, Merrill J. (66-37) (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - Stanford University - Bray, James O. (64-26) (Box 11, Folder 119)
    - Stanford University - Frake, Charles O. (66-36) (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - Stanford University - Hanna, Paul R. (63-47) (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - Stanford University - Siegel, Bernard J. (65-22) (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - State University College, New Paltz - Campbell, Joan M. (64-32) (Box 11, Folder 123)
    - State University College, New Paltz - Campbell, Joan M. (66-4) (Box 11, Folder 124)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo - Haupert, John S. (66-33) (Box 11, Folder 125)
    - University of Texas - Mayfield, R.C. (66-43) (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - University of Texas - Mayfield, Robert C. (67-49) (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - Texas A&M University - McNeely, J.G. (63-34) (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Texas A&M University - Nelson, Bardin H. (65-2) (Box 12, Folder 129)
    - Texas A&M University - Nelson, Bardin H. (67-41) (Box 12, Folder 130)
    - University of Toronto - Birch, J.W. (65-23) (Box 12, Folder 131)
    - Vanderbilt University - Long, Millard F. (64-28) (Box 12, Folder 132)
    - Vanderbilt University - Nicholls, William H. (65-16) (Box 12, Folder 133)
    - Vanderbilt University - Nicholls, William H. (65-16) (Box 12, Folder 134)
    - Vanderbilt University - Sahota, Gians (66-17) (Box 12, Folder 135)
    - Vanderbilt University - Sahota, Gians (66-17) (Box 12, Folder 136)
    - Washington University - Bennett, John W. (65-38) (Box 12, Folder 137)
    - Washington University - Bennett, John W. (66-38) (Box 13, Folder 138)
    - West Virginia University - Moris, Jon R. (65-8) (Box 13, Folder 139)
    - West Virginia University - Moris, Jon R. (65-8) (Box 13, Folder 140)
    - Williams College - Eddie, Scott (65-36) (Box 13, Folder 141)
    - Williams College - Eddie, Scott (67-9) (Box 13, Folder 142)
    - University of Wisconsin - Clark, Robert C. (66-23) (Box 13, Folder 143)
    - University of Wisconsin - Cook, Hugh L. (65-29) (Box 13, Folder 144)
    - University of Wisconsin - Day, Richard H. (66-15) (Box 13, Folder 145)
    - University of Wisconsin - Day, Richard H. (66-15) (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - University of Wisconsin - Flinn, William L. (66-35 (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - University of Wisconsin - Haller, Archibald O. (67-25) (Box 14, Folder 148)
    - University of Wisconsin - Miracle, Marvin P. (65-47) (Box 14, Folder 149)
    - University of Wisconsin - Parsons, K.H. (63-8) (Box 14, Folder 150)
    - University of Wisconsin - Wilkening, E.A. (66-24) (Box 14, Folder 151)
- Research and Training Network, 1953-1977; 3
  Series 3 is arranged in 3 subseries:
  Subseries 2 - Workshops Subseries 3 - Grants Subseries 5 - Publications
  This series does not have a Subseries 1 or a Subseries 4.
  The Research and Training Network (RTN) was a program to facilitate interaction and cooperation among American professors, technical aid agency personnel, and non-Western scholars on problems of agricultural development. The goals were the improvement of theory and research with respect to agricultural development and graduate training in the social sciences for students from developing areas. This series includes material pertaining to workshops sponsored by the RTN, grants, and publications.
  - Research and Training Network - Workshops, 3.2
    - Agricultural Programs Administration - Planning Session, December 7-8, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Rural Marketing and Domestic Trade, December 14, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Rural Employment and Income Distribution, December 16-18, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Development and Management of Agricultural Research Systems, December 18, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - International Trade, January 15-16, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Student, January 18-19, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Water Resource Development, February 12-13, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Development Strategies for Low-Income Farmers - Planning Session, February 19, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Agricultural Policy Course, March 22-23, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Agricultural Policy Course, April 2-3, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Rural Marketing and Domestic Trade, April 8-9, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Land Policy Course, April 29-30, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - International Trade, May 6-7, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Agricultural Sector Analysis and Planning, May 17-18, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Agricultural Sector Analysis and Planning, May 17-18, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Agricultural Sector Analysis and Planning, May 17-18, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - International Trade, May 24, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Interrelationships Between Population, Employment and Economic Growth, May 26-27, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Land Policy Course - Planning Session, June 14, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Water Resource Development, August 23-24, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Small Farmer Development Strategies, September 13-15, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Small Farmer Development Strategies, September 13-15, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Small Farmer Development Strategies, September 13-15, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Small Farmer Development Strategies, September 13-15, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Teaching the Administration of Agricultural Development Program, September 17, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Land Policy Course Syllabus, October 1, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Rural Marketing, October 7-9, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Rural Marketing, October 7-9, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Production Incentives, October 13-15, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Education and Rural Development, October 21-22, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - International Trade - Planning Session, November 19, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Sector Analysis Simulation - Planning Session, December 1, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Interrelationships Between Population, Employment and Growth, December 2-3, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Water Resource Development, December 6-8, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Roles of Sociologists in Agricultural Development, December 9-10, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Teaching the Administration of Agricultural Development Programs, December 11-12, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Strategies for Agricultural Development in the 1970's, December 13-18, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Agricultural Research Priorities, January 17-18, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Problems of Verification and Policy Simulation in Sectoral Models for Less Developed Countries, February 28-29, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Problems of Verification and Policy Simulation in Sectoral Models for Less Developed Countries, February 28-29, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Forestry Research and Economic Development, March 27-28, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Administration of Agricultural Programs, April 4-8, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Administration of Agricultural Programs, April 4-8, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Agricultural Credit for Small Farmers, April 6-7, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Agricultural Credit for Small Farmers, April 6-7, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Agricultural Credit for Small Farmers, April 6-7, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Market Development and Equity Workshop, April 13-15, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Market Development and Equity Workshop, April 13-15, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Production Incentives Workshop, April 17-18, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Water Resource - Planning Session, April 21, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Agricultural Sector Analysis and Planning, May 1-3, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Land Policy Course, May 1-2, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Contribution of Foreign Agri-Business Firms in Agricultural Development, May 23-25, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Contribution of Foreign Agri-Business Firms in Agricultural Development, May 23-25, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Land Policy for the Developing Countries Course, June 19-July 14, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Land Policy for the Developing Countries Course, June 19-July 14, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Production Incentives, June 20-22, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Production Incentives, June 21, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Gotsch Seminar - Planning Session, September 5, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Land Policy for the Developing Countries Course, September 19, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Rural Marketing, October 2-4, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Rural Marketing, October 2-4, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Production Incentives, October 12, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Management of Irrigation Systems for the Farm, October 15-18, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Management of Irrigation Systems for the Farm, October 15-18, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Socio-Economic Research Issues in Fisheries Development, October 25-27, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Application of Recursive Decision Systems in Agricultural Sector Analysis, November 1-3, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Application of Recursive Decision Systems in Agricultural Sector Analysis, November 1-3, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Economics of Nutrition, February 2-3, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Trade, Agricultural and Economic Development, February 13-14, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Trade, Agricultural and Economic Development, February 13-14, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Trade, Agricultural and Economic Development, February 13-14, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Political Economy of Rural Development, February 16, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Economics of Farm Mechanization and Processing in Developing Countries, March 23-24, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Economics of Farm Mechanization and Processing in Developing Countries, March 23-24, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Agricultural Marketing, April 8-11, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Regional Agricultural Development Planning, April 17-19, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Regional Agricultural Development Planning, April 17-19, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Trade and Development, May 14-15, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Human Resources and Nutrition Economics, May 18-19, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Production Incentives, June 18-July 24, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Production Incentives, June 18-July 24, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Rural Public Works, July 25, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Production Economics for Non-Economists, July 26, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Nutrition, August 1, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Serving Agriculture as an Administrator, November 7-8, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Serving Agriculture as an Administrator, November 7-8, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Nutrition Policy and Programming Research, November 12-14, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Land Reform, December 17, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Research and Training Network - Grants, 3.3
    - Abdullah Bin Ujang, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Akhand, Muhammad, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Allahabad Agricultural Institute - Agricultural Extension Training and Evaluation, 1955-1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Allahabad Agricultural Institute - Field Trips, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Allahabad Agricultural Institute - Pal - Tour, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Allahabad Agricultural Institute - Singh, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Allahabad Agricultural Institute - Teaching Materials, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Allahabad Agricultural Institute - Wycliffe - Farm Income Study, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - American Committee for the Third World Congress of Agricultural Librarians, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - American Friends Service Committee - International Student Seminars in Japan, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - American-Korean Foundation - Choo and Chung - Travel, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - American Universities Field Staff, 1955-1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - American University of Beirut - Hasanullah - Field Research, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - American University of Beirut - Pakistani Field Work, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - American University of Beirut - Rahman - Field Research, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Anthropological and Ethological Sciences Congress - Travel - Husin, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Archaeological Survey of Burma - Pagan Restoration (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Archaeological Survey of Burma - Pagan Restoration, 1960-1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Asia Society - McCray - Travel, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Association of Colleges of Agriculture in the Philippines - Agricultural Project Development Course, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Association of Colleges of Agriculture in the Philippines - Cooperatives Seminar, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Association of Colleges of Agriculture in the Philippines - Farm Management Syllabus, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Association of Colleges of Agriculture in the Philippines - Women Agriculture Graduates, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Australian National University - Employment of Malayan Padi Farms, 1962, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Australian National University - Kanungo - Travel, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Balwant Rajput College, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Ban, Sung Hwan, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Bicol Development Planning Board, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Bicol Development Planning Board, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Bicol Development Planning Board, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Bicol Development Planning Board - Aid in the Establishment of Development Procedures in the Bicol, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Bokhari, Nazir Abbas, 1957, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Bratton, Charles A. - Travel, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Buck, J. L. - "Land Utilization in China", 1956-1959, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Bustrillos, Nena R. - Travel, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - University of California - Pilot Project, 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Castillo, Gelia - Travel, 1963-1965, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Castillo, Gelia - Travel, 1963-1965, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - University of Ceylon - Agricultural Economics Research Unit, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - University of Ceylon - Agricultural Economics Research Unit, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - University of Ceylon - Agricultural Economics Research Unit, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - University of Ceylon - Agricultural Economics Research Unit, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 42)